https://www.passporthealthusa.com/privacy-policy/

HomeAboutCompany HistoryExecutive TeamCareersContact UsCustomer FeedbackFAQMedia KitMission StatementPrivacy PolicyBlogsMainEmployer SolutionsPassports and Visas CloseDestination AdviceTop DestinationsCOVID-19 TestingDomestic COVID-19 RestrictionsInternational COVID-19 RestrictionsFit to FlyBrazilChinaCosta RicaIndiaKenyaPeruPhilippinesSouth AfricaThailandVietnamDestination Advice Tips and recommendations for healthy travel to any destination:
Afghanistan
Albania
Algeria
American Samoa
Andorra
Angola
Anguilla
Antarctica
Zimbabwe
CloseTravel MedicineTravel Medical ServicesVaccines for TravelTravel Health ConsultingTravelers’ Diarrhea MedicineDengue Fever PreventionMalaria MedicationChikungunya PreventionZika Virus PreventionCoronavirusEbola VirusTravel Health AlertsAdditional Travel ServicesTravel PhysicalsMotion Sickness MedicineTravel InsurancePhysician Referral ProgramOnline Store CloseVaccinesOverviewAnthraxChickenpoxCholeraHepatitis AHepatitis BHuman Papillomavirus (HPV)Japanese EncephalitisMalaria InformationMeasles – Mumps – Rubella (MMR)MeningitisPneumoniaPolioRabiesShinglesTetanus-Diphtheria-PertussisTyphoidYellow FeverInfluenza (The Flu) Learn more about your flu vaccine options
Flublok®: Egg Free, Cell Based
High Dose
Quadrivalent
Routine TestsCOVID-19 TestingTB TestsTiter TestingRoutine VaccinationsOverview CloseCOVID-19COVID-19 ServicesCOVID-19 TestingCOVID-19 Domestic RestrictionsCOVID-19 International RestrictionsCOVID-19 VaccineFit to FlyFit for Duty CloseFor EmployersCorporate Wellness SolutionsCOVID-19 ServicesOccupational VaccinesOnsite Flu ClinicsOnsite Biometric ScreeningsEmployee WellnessEmployment PhysicalsCorporate Travel SolutionsTravel Medicine and VaccinationsPassport and Visa ServicesPre-Deployment Exams CloseOnline StorePassport Health StoreCOVID-19 Protection KitTravelers’ Diarrhea KitsMosquito Repellents CloseLocations
Canada Locations
Mexico Locations
CloseLocations
United States
Choose your state
Alabama
Alaska
Arizona
1. General
Passport Health, LLC, and its affiliated franchises throughout the United States, respect the privacy of every individual who visits www.passporthealthusa.com (the “Web Site” or “Site”). The privacy of your personal information is very important to us. This Privacy Policy is designed to outline the types of information we collect, how we
use that information, and the circumstances under which we may share that information. This Policy will also tell you what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or shared. If you have any questions about our policy, please email us at privacy@passporthealthusa.com.
2. Your Acceptance of These Terms
Passport Health reserves the right to change its practices at any time, may update the Privacy Statement at any time and has no other obligation of notice of such changes. By using the Web Site, you signify your consent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use the Site. Your continued use of the Web Site following the posting of changes to its terms means you accept those changes.
3. Personally Identifiable Information
There are cases where we may ask you for personally identifiable information such as your name, mailing address, email address, and/or telephone number. We request personally identifiable information for online appointment booking, online travel supply purchases, feedback forms, surveys, our blog sign up and for other services that require registration or subscription. We will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily. When you provide us with personally identifiable information, Passport Health may:
store and process that information to better understand your needs, customize your experience, and improve our products and services;
use that information to contact you via email and postal mail for informational, marketing, and promotional purposes;
disclose that information to third parties who need such information to provide products and services that you have requested;
disclose that information to third parties when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Passport Health’s rights or property, other users of the Web Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; and
Disclose that information to third parties when we believe in good faith that the law requires it
We limit the ways in which we use the information you provide to us.
Except as stated in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise stated at the time personally-identifiable information is gathered, we will not provide personally-identifiable information to third parties, although certain non-personally identifiable user information may be provided in aggregate form to third parties.
4. Financial Information
Passport Health may ask you for your credit card number and expiration date when you order goods or services from our travel accessories Web Site or to book an appointment online. We will use your credit card information for processing orders and/or reserving your appointment and may share this information with credit card processing companies and any other third party that may need the information to process your orders. These organizations have their own privacy and data collection practices, and we have no responsibility for these independent policies.
5. Non-Personally Identifiable Information
Passport Health may also collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. This type of information includes your age, gender, zip code, area code, interests, and preferences. We will not collect any such information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily. We may share this information in the aggregate with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third
Parties. For example, we may inform a partner that the users of the Web Site are x percent females and y percent males. These data are used to customize our Site’s content. We will also use the data to make visits to the Site easier, quicker, and better for you and our other users. We also may track certain information about your visit to the Web Site, including (without limitation) pages viewed, clickstreams, and searches. Such information is gathered in aggregate and is not linked to any specific users.
6. Other Special Circumstances
Contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions to the Site may have separate privacy practices with regard to the information collected in connection with entering or participating in any such event. You will have a choice of whether or not you would like to allow certain information to be shared with third parties that may have a product or service of interest to you.
7. Modification of Information and Opt-Out
If you registered to receive Passport Health blog emails, we may occasionally send you e-mails about, for example, current outbreaks that may affect travel destinations, new vaccines entering the market and new products and services we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such mailings, you may click on “Unsubscribe” at the bottom of the email.
8. Information Collected Automatically
Passport Health may also automatically collect non-personally identifiable information about your use of the Web Site, such as the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account), the date and time you access the Site, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Site. This information will not be linked to personally-identifiable information. We may use this information to analyze and enhance our Web Site and for security purposes, and we may aggregate this information and share the aggregated information with business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.
9. Information Placed Automatically On Your Computer’s Hard Drive
When you view the Web Site, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a “Cookie” or similar file and will help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor the Web Site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. (Remember, however, that blocking or deleting Cookies may limit your ability to access some or all of the features and services of the Web Site.)
Learn more about our cookie policy here
10. HIPAA Compliance
Passport Health adheres to HIPAA. Before your visit to Passport Health, you will have to sign and agree to our HIPAA Policy and Consent Form. The form will be made available to you electronically once you make an appointment at Passport Health. A copy of this form is also available at each of our offices and can be completed at the time of the appointment if it was not completed electronically prior to the appointment. You can view the form by clicking here.
11. Children
The Web Site is not directed at individuals under thirteen years of age, and Passport Health does not intend to collect any personally identifiable information from such individuals.
12. Links to Other Web Sites
Be aware that some of Passport Health’s partners have links on the Site that take you to other sites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Passport Health hopes that all third parties involved adhere to Passport Health’s policies regarding the privacy of Passport Health’s users. However, this Privacy Policy does not cover third party data collection practices, and Passport Health does not assume any responsibility for any actions of third parties.
13. Security
The importance of security of all personally identifiable information associated with our users is of the utmost concern to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we can’t ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. However, once we receive your personally identifiable information, we will take reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.
As a client, you will be asked to complete an online medical history form through our EMR system (Passageware). The information kept in the EMR is encrypted and password protected. You will be assigned a temporary password and login so you can access the EMR to complete your medical history form prior to your appointment. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Passport Health will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Remember to sign out of your account on the Web Site and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This will ensure that others cannot access our personal information and correspondence if your computer is accessible to others, if you share a computer with someone else, or if you use a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe.
14. Whom to Contact
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy and its enforcement by Passport Health, its employees or its franchisees, you should contact Passport Health at:
Privacy Issues
Passport Health, LLC
668 N 44th St
Ste 100W
Phoenix, AZ 85008
privacy@passporthealthusa.com
Do you need your passport or visa in a hurry?
Get your travel documents ASAP!
Why Use a Travel Medicine Specialist?
Countless Considerations, Even for Just One Destination!
We Can Answer
Which vaccines are required?
Which vaccines may be recommended?
Which medications do I need?
What Travel Supplies do I need?
And much more
Do you need travel vaccines?
Schedule an appointment with your local Passport Health Travel Medicine Specialist
Latest health alerts for international travelers
INFLUENZA WorldwideJune '19 – According to the CDC, annual vaccination against seasonal influenza is recommended for ...YELLOW FEVER in Argentina, Brazil, Congo, Republic of the, Nigeria, Peru, Suriname, UgandaJune '19 -
Case numbers for yellow fever are thought to be greatly under-reported; the World Health...
More Health Alert Information»
Recent Blog Posts
How Does Measles Spread? A New Study Gives Answers
The Necessary and Unfortunate Identity of “Patient Zero”
What Was The Plague of Justinian? How A Single Outbreak Killed 10% Of The World’s Population.
Tips To Stay Safe While Traveling Alone
Blog Archives
Blog Archives
Select Month
September 2020  (2)
August 2020  (4)
July 2020  (5)
June 2020  (2)
May 2020  (5)
April 2020  (3)
March 2020  (10)
February 2020  (13)
January 2020  (18)
December 2019  (10)
November 2019  (10)
October 2019  (7)
September 2019  (12)
August 2019  (10)
July 2019  (9)
June 2019  (9)
May 2019  (9)
April 2019  (13)
March 2019  (14)
February 2019  (12)
January 2019  (14)
December 2018  (13)
November 2018  (13)
October 2018  (16)
September 2018  (13)
August 2018  (18)
July 2018  (16)
June 2018  (16)
May 2018  (17)
April 2018  (14)
March 2018  (12)
February 2018  (12)
January 2018  (15)
December 2017  (14)
November 2017  (17)
October 2017  (12)
September 2017  (10)
August 2017  (13)
July 2017  (9)
June 2017  (13)
May 2017  (8)
April 2017  (2)
March 2017  (3)
February 2017  (3)
January 2017  (4)
December 2016  (4)
November 2016  (7)
October 2016  (6)
September 2016  (1)
August 2016  (7)
July 2016  (5)
June 2016  (4)
May 2016  (5)
April 2016  (3)
March 2016  (3)
February 2016  (5)
January 2016  (4)
December 2015  (5)
November 2015  (6)
October 2015  (8)
September 2015  (15)
August 2015  (11)
July 2015  (8)
June 2015  (8)
May 2015  (6)
April 2015  (2)
March 2015  (9)
February 2015  (14)
January 2015  (15)
December 2014  (15)
November 2014  (13)
October 2014  (17)
September 2014  (6)
August 2014  (8)
July 2014  (7)
June 2014  (5)
May 2014  (5)
April 2014  (2)
March 2014  (4)
February 2014  (2)
January 2014  (2)
December 2013  (2)
November 2013  (1)
October 2013  (3)
September 2013  (1)
June 2013  (1)
May 2013  (1)
December 2012  (1)
Schedule Your Appointment:
Questions? Please call or E-mail Us
FIRST CLASS MEDICAL CARE FOR TRAVEL ANYWHERE®
Connect With Us:
